

Cristiano Santos

07388649044 | **E:** cristiano_santos93@hotmail.com 20 Duke Street, Southampton SO14 3ET

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Trilingual and highly motivated recent bachelor's degree recipient with more than 10 years of experience working in a team in different industries in different countries looking to kickstart my career in Web Development. During my course, the design and development of an app was very interesting and I found myself having fun doing it. Interested in further developing my JavaScript and React skills to create even better Web Applications.

WORK HISTORY

DISHWASHER

02/2020 - CURRENT

Bidvest Noonan | Southampton

- Work as part of a team to insure all dishes and cutlery is clean and ready to use
- Insure all machines are working properly and report any faults to the relevant Supervisor
- Was able to quickly adapt to the role and after about 1 year was promoted to team leader.

FLOOR ASSISTANT / USHER

10/2019 - 08/2020

Showcase Cinema de Lux | Southampton

- Worked as part of a team greeting the customers to check their tickets and providing the best possible service to make their cinema experience positive and memorable by clarifying any questions the customers had.
- On busy weekend days, handled over 100 customers

BUILDING CONSTRUCTION / BRICKLAYER

08/2016 - 07/2019

Johann Volonte AG | Nunningen, Solothurn

- Worked as part of a team in buildings construction and road repairs
- Worked in a 2 man team in the removal and then renewal of the water pipelines in a Retirement Home
- Handled communications when working with private customers.

AUXILIARY WORKER

11/2014 - 07/2016

Arifi Naturstein AG | Reinach, Basel-Stadt

 Worked as part of a small team to build walls, floors and other stone related jobs

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js
- GitHub

• Flutter mobile development

- UX/UI design
- Front and back end development

EDUCATION (

BSc | Computing

Expected in 05/2022

Southampton Solent University, Southampton

Learned:

- Problem Solving though Programming,
- UX,
- Web Technologies,
- Web App development,
- Human Computer Interaction,
- and much more.

NVQ Level 3 | Technical Renewable Energies and Solar Systems 06/2012 Escola Serafim Leite, Sao Joao da Madeira

INTERESTS ()

- Interested in Meta and often enjoy using my Meta Quest 2 device.
 - A fan of Airsoft where I enjoy a nice day of exercise with friends while shooting each other with fake guns.
 - Also a fan of Gaming